<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>InStat on</title><link>https://lakings-graph.com/tags/InStat/</link><description>Recent content in InStat on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://lakings-graph.com/tags/InStat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A new look at the new look LA Kings power play</title><link>https://lakings-graph.com/A-new-look-at-the-new-look-LA-Kings-power-play/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lakings-graph.com/A-new-look-at-the-new-look-LA-Kings-power-play/</guid><description>A new look at the new look LA Kings power play Date Site External Link 2022-11-14 [[Hockey Royalty]] A new look at the new look LA Kings power play Contributors [[Joe Patarino]] Summary The LA Kings showed off a different setup with their top powerplay unit in Saturday’s 4-3 win over the Detroit Red Wings.</description></item><item><title>Kevin Fiala - a full scale breakdown on the newest member of the LA Kings</title><link>https://lakings-graph.com/Kevin-Fiala-a-full-scale-breakdown-on-the-newest-member-of-the-LA-Kings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lakings-graph.com/Kevin-Fiala-a-full-scale-breakdown-on-the-newest-member-of-the-LA-Kings/</guid><description>Kevin Fiala - a full scale breakdown on the newest member of the LA Kings Date Site External Link 2022-07-04 [[Hockey Royalty]] Kevin Fiala - a full scale breakdown on the newest member of the LA Kings Contributors [[Pavel Maliouguine]] Summary The LA Kings made an early splash into the 2022 NHL off-season with their trade for Minnesota Wild forward Kevin Fiala.</description></item><item><title>LA Kings - Digging into Quinton Byfields play while in the AHL</title><link>https://lakings-graph.com/LA-Kings-Digging-into-Quinton-Byfields-play-while-in-the-AHL/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lakings-graph.com/LA-Kings-Digging-into-Quinton-Byfields-play-while-in-the-AHL/</guid><description>LA Kings - Digging into Quinton Byfields play while in the AHL Date Site External Link 2022-11-29 [[Hockey Royalty]] LA Kings - Digging into Quinton Byfields play while in the AHL Contributors [[Joe Patarino]] Summary After playing in eight NHL games with the LA Kings to start the 2022-23 season, Quinton Byfield was sent to the AHL’s Ontario Reign after missing time due to an illness.</description></item><item><title>Three ways the LA Kings can improve the powerplay</title><link>https://lakings-graph.com/Three-ways-the-LA-Kings-can-improve-the-powerplay/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lakings-graph.com/Three-ways-the-LA-Kings-can-improve-the-powerplay/</guid><description>Three ways the LA Kings can improve the powerplay Date Site External Link 2022-11-12 [[Hockey Royalty]] Three ways the LA Kings can improve the powerplay Contributors [[Pavel Maliouguine]] Summary In the 2021-22 NHL season, the most significant discussion point for the LA Kings was the lack of success on the powerplay.</description></item><item><title>Video breakdown of defensive zone struggles of the LA Kings</title><link>https://lakings-graph.com/Video-breakdown-of-defensive-zone-struggles-of-the-LA-Kings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lakings-graph.com/Video-breakdown-of-defensive-zone-struggles-of-the-LA-Kings/</guid><description>Video breakdown of defensive zone struggles of the LA Kings Date Site External Link 2022-11-17 [[Hockey Royalty]] Video breakdown of defensive zone struggles of the LA Kings Contributors [[Joe Patarino]] Summary The LA Kings have struggled to keep pucks out of their net through the first 18 games of the 2022-23 season.</description></item><item><title>What went right for the LA Kings defensively in Edmonton</title><link>https://lakings-graph.com/What-went-right-for-the-LA-Kings-defensively-in-Edmonton/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lakings-graph.com/What-went-right-for-the-LA-Kings-defensively-in-Edmonton/</guid><description>What went right for the LA Kings defensively in Edmonton Date Site External Link 2022-11-18 [[Hockey Royalty]] What went right for the LA Kings defensively in Edmonton Contributors [[Joe Patarino]] Summary After a game with a litany of defensive zone breakdowns in Calgary, the LA Kings shored things up in Edmonton en route to a stingy 3-1 win.</description></item></channel></rss>